Frank Donnelly

frank.steven.donnelly@gmail.com (619)952-8514

Profile

I am an ambitious full-stack developer, who would like to join a team of like minded programmers. Skilled with all aspects of MERN Full Stack development. My previous work experience in the financial industry has provided me with excellent customer service skills, attention to detail, and the ability to plan and organize to achieve the goals set before me.

Skills

- HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript, JQuery, React, Redux, MongoDB, Firebase, MySQL
- Bootstrap, FontAwesome, Materialize-UI, Semantic-UI
- Custom APIs using Express, Node.js, Next.js
- MVC, REST, JSON
- Testing with Jest, Postman

My Portfolio Link: https://fsdonnelly.github.io/donnelly-portfolio/

Experience

Harbor of Hope Women's Cancer Foundation

https://harborofhopewcf.org/

(March 2019) Developed and published a website utilizing GoDaddy's web builder, for a non-profit organization in the Long Beach CA area. I keep the site updated with current events and help the organization implement new features. Currently creating a full-stack website using MERN to replace the GoDaddy site in the future.

Loan Officer

(June 2018 to August 2018) Bridgeview Bank Mortgage Company (February 2018 to May 2018) Pacific Union Financial LLC DBA LoanIt (August 2017 to January 2018) Prime Mortgage Lending & Equity Services (October 2016 to March 2017) American Financing Corporation (June 2015 to November 2016) Catalyst Mortgage/ Ignite Lending 4444 Mission Blvd., San Diego, CA 92109

- Worked in a small call center environment doing out bound calls on leads provided by third party vendors.
 Main duties included taking complete application, providing excellent customer service, following up on needed documents
- Working from home as a remote Mortgage Consultant taking inbound calls, following up with online leads, and making sure that files move forward in a timely fashion. Closing 5 to 8 loans a month consistently. I enjoy working in a team environment and at the same time work very hard independently.
- Assisted Regional Vice President of Sales by following up loan status with production, and document status
 with clients. Explained terms and details of loans to clients in professional and timely fashion. Generated my
 own leads through personal contacts, business relationships, and marketing strategies.

Additional Skills and Accomplishments

- Familiar with rules and regulations pertaining to RESPA and TRID
- Proficient in Microsoft Office, Excel, Word, POINTO, and ENCOMPAS

Certificates

- Certified Full Stack Web Developer (UCSD 2019)
- Multiple certificates in Web Development from Udemy

Education

UCSD Extension Campus (2019) San Diego State University (2000 - 2004) Mesa Junior College in San Diego (1998 - 2000)